https://www.pdicorp.com/terms-of-use/

Smiths Group PLC Privacy Policy
Smiths Group plc (“Smiths”) is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We will maintain the privacy of and protect your personal information in accordance with Smiths’ normal procedures and all applicable law. Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal information when you use our website (the “Website”).
Collection and Use of Personal Information
There are two ways we may collect and use information about you:
1. Information you voluntarily provide
Smiths collects the information you voluntarily provide when you use the Website, for example, the information you provide when you sign up to receive Email Alerts, when you ask us a question or email us with feedback, or maybe when you complete a survey. Some of this information will be personal information and Smiths will only use it for the purposes for which you provide it. For example, if you provide your email address when you sign up to receive Email Alerts, we use your email address to deliver the Email Alerts you request. Note that the Email Alerts contain an “unsubscribe” option in case you want to discontinue receiving the alerts at any time.
2. Information sent to us by your web browser
Every time you log onto the Website we store details of your visit, including your IP address. We collect only the domain name, but not the email address of visitors to the Website, unless you voluntarily provide it. This enables us to determine what you looked at, whether the page request was successful or not, and which browser your machine used to view the pages. The use of this data is primarily for statistical and monitoring purposes and helps us to evaluate use and performance and improve the content of the Website. Please note that we do not use Cookies.
Transfer of Personal Information
We may from time to time transfer some of the information we collect to other Smiths’ offices, affiliates, agents or appointed representatives. Some of Smiths’ offices and those of our affiliates, agents or representatives are located in countries outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including the United States, which do not have the same level of data protection that exists in the EEA. Whenever we transfer your personal information to countries outside of the EEA, we will ensure that your privacy rights are protected and that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the UK Data Protection Act 1998.
Sharing and Retaining Personal Information
We do not sell, rent, or exchange the personal information we collect from you with any third parties outside the Smiths’ group of companies, without your consent. Where we share your personal information with other Smiths’ business units, they will use your information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected and consistent with this Privacy Policy and all applicable data protection and privacy laws.
We will only disclose your personal information to third parties to: comply with the law or regulatory authorities, enforce or apply our terms of business, protect our rights and those of our users, or with your consent. In such cases we will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information.
Smiths may also share your personal information with third parties we hire to perform support services for us. There third parties are required to use the personal information we share with them only to perform services on our behalf and to treat your personal information as strictly confidential.
Smiths retains the personal information collected on the Website only as long as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, or as permitted by applicable law.
Our goal is to provide you with the best possible experience on the Website.
Access to Special Content and Services
Some areas and content on the Website, such as Smiths’ Email Alerts require you to register with Smiths in order to access. If you choose not to register and provide personal information, you may still use most of the Website. For Email Alerts, customer information may be changed by the registered user at any time by accessing the Smiths’ Email Alerts section of the Website.
Security
All the data we collect from you on the Website is protected against unauthorized access. We maintain appropriate security measures and procedures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you on the Website. We will not be responsible for breaches of our security beyond our reasonable control.
Links to Third Party Sites
Where there are links on the Website to other sites, not operated by Smiths, the content of those linked sites is not covered by this privacy policy and is not endorsed by Smiths. These other sites will have separate privacy and data collection practices. We do not have responsibility or liability for these independent policies nor for the content, security or privacy practices of those other sites.
Consent
By using the Website, you signify your agreement to be bound by the Smiths Group plc Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not use the Website or submit any personally identifiable information.
Contact
We strive to ensure that the information we maintain about our visitors is accurate, current and complete. If you have any questions regarding this policy or if you wish to review, update or correct your personal information, we can be contacted by mail or phone as follows:
Smiths Group plc
2nd Floor
Cardinal Place
80 Victoria Street
London
SW1E 5JL
T: +44 (0) 20 7808 5500
Notification of Changes
This privacy policy was last updated on 15 September 2005. We reserve the right to amend or vary this policy at any time and the revised policy will apply from the date posted on the Website. You accept that by doing this, Smiths has provided you with sufficient notice of the amendment or variation. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. It is located at https://www.smiths.com.
Smiths Group plc is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998.
Solutions
Data Center
Construction & Infrastructure
Education
Industrial
Medical
Military
Retail
Contact Us
The PDI Corp website uses cookies to give you the best possible user experience. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. To find out more about cookies and how to manage them, please read our Privacy and Cookie Policy.
Accept
